Kareem El-Zomor

Egypt



karim67899@gmail.com



01111258669



linkedin.com/in/kareem-el-zomor-0a2a94150

Summary

I am a Front End developer building websites and web applications. I specialize in HTML5, CSS3 & JavaScript, I'm also studying React and have a passion to be in the mastery level of Frontend Development. Take a look at my work! https://github.com/KareeMagdyy

Experience



st Customer Service Advisor

SiriusXM Canada May 2019 - Jan 2021 (1 year 9 months)

Customer Service Advisor

Convergys

May 2019 - Jan 2021 (1 year 9 months)

Senior Closer

Global Expo Travel Sep 2018 - Apr 2019 (8 months)

Sales Representative

Exhibitors Housing Management Apr 2016 - Sep 2018 (2 years 6 months)

Data Miner

Freelance

Jan 2015 - Mar 2016 (1 year 3 months)

Customer Service Representative

Vodafone

Jun 2014 - Dec 2014 (7 months)

Education



Cairo University

Bachelor's degree, Business/Commerce, General 2011 - 2019

Licenses & Certifications

- Web Development Challenger Track Udacity
 ZAKKLN9Y
- **Learn HTML & CSS By Examples** Udemy UC-1969045f-bed9-4971-b434
- Web Development Full Stack PHP CLS Learning Solutions 013223
- Succeeding in Web Development: Full Stack and Front End LinkedIn AePsxFPjBvC9g_bNYcdoxjAHTadK
- Time Management: Working from Home LinkedIn
- Front-End Web UI Frameworks and Tools: Bootstrap 4 The Hong Kong University of Science and Technology
 WZPJ8YT2CNVX
- Front-End Development Track Udacity
 R4DKKDCQ
- CSS The Complete Guide 2021 (incl. Flexbox, Grid & Sass) Udemy UC-3f36e23f-1896-4eeb-b6e3-82b3cdd189b3
- (A) Responsive Web Design freeCodeCamp
- HTML & CSS IBM

Skills

Website Building • Adobe Photoshop • Web Development • Time Management • HTML5 • Bootstrap • Cascading Style Sheets (CSS) • JavaScript • GitHub • Git